The carpet'sthin,
the paneling isbrown.
She's got her stereo cranked uploud.
Her parents areout,
they're at TheCrown.
So we can own this entiretown.
She's got her bare feet sliding on thefloor.
Right past the posters taped to herdoor.
The little green light on the CD player is the only thing I'm focused on besidesher.
She bounces on herheels,
a little bitshy.
Then the fuzz guitar kicksin,
she closes hereyes.
One,
two,
three,
four.
She's dancing to Sloan in thebasement.
She knows all thewords,
every newarrangement.
She's got her armsup,
singing to theceiling.
I'm just sitting on thecouch,
loving thisfeeling.
She's allright.
Ooh.
She spins around and her red hairflies.
A perfect blurry mess before myeyes.
She's got thismove,
it's a jerky collision of puremomentum,
nodecision.
She's closing hereyes,
she's mouthing the parts of all the songs she knows byheart.
She's jumping on the beat then stops on adime.
She's in her ownworld,
and she's outside oftime.
And Iknow,
I know she's not afraid to be who she wants and break all therules.
Here it comesnow.
She's dancing to Weezer in thebasement.
She's playing air guitar for the replacement of all the static on theradio.
Inever,
ever want togo.
And she's allright.
She's allright.
Ooh.
The song breaksdown,
the music getslow.
She stops and looks atme,
and I just know this is the only place I wannabe.
The feedback'sbuilding,
one,
two,
three.
She smiles alittle,
and drums kickin.
She grabs my hand andsays,
"Getup,"
and starts tospin.
We're dancing to Sam Roberts in thebasement.
She knows all thewords,
every newarrangement.
She's got her armsup,
singing to theceiling.
I'm on my feetnow,
I'm loving thisfeeling.
And she's allright.
She's allright.
Ooh.
Dancing to astereo.
She's allright.
Just her and mehere.
Allright.
That red in herhair.
She's allright.