<foreign music.
Well,
the world has wonders seven theysay.
But they haven't seen your legstoday.
They go on for miles like a highwayline.
So smooth andsilky,
lord,
they'refine.
From your pretty little ankles to your upperthighs.
They're the sweetest sight for these oldeyes.
Yeah,
they're long andlovely,
sleek andstrong.
I could stare at them all daylong.
But,
oh,
your tiny kneecaps.
They're like little bottlecaps.
Just sitting there so neat andsmall.
They're the cutest part ofall.
Yeah,
your tiny kneecaps.
Maybe they're my favoritemaps.
Leading me toparadise.
Oh,
those knees are mightynice.
When you wear those cutoffs straight at theend.
That's when my poor heart just can'tpretend.
It's a masterpiece ofbiology.
What those lovely legs just do tome.
Some men likemountains,
some like thesea.
But your perfect stems are the view forme.
So graceful when youwalk,
so fine when youstand.
The best pair of legs in all theland.
But,
oh,
your tiny kneecaps.
They're like little bottlecaps.
Just sitting there so neat andsmall.
They're the cutest part ofall.
Yeah,
your tiny kneecaps.
Maybe they're my favoritemaps.
Leading me toparadise.
Oh,
those knees are mightynice.
Now people write poems about youreyes.
And your lovely head and mysurprise.
They can have yoursmile,
they can have yourhands.
But only I trulyunderstand.
The realattraction,
the mainevent.
It's all about your tiny kneecaps.
They're like little bottlecaps.
Just sitting there so neat andsmall.
They're the cutest part ofall.
Yeah,
your tiny kneecaps.
Maybe they're my favoritemaps.
Leading me toparadise.
Oh,
those knees are mightynice.
Yeah.
Those little bittyknees.
Love'em.
Mm.