The cabin lights were settledin.
The family fastasleep.
The fireplace wasembers.
A promise I couldn'tkeep.
Isaid,
"Goodnight,
my darling" and hit the flannelsheets.
You stayed out by the fireglow.
Sipping somethingsweet.
A bottle full ofcinnamon,
they call itFireball.
You said it's just soeasy.
Leaning on thewall.
You didn't see thedanger.
The sugarydisguise.
Just the dancing flames reflected in youreyes.
Oh,
but3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then amoan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plasticthrone.
And I was your humble servant in the palemoonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all mymight.
It wasn't wine androses.
It wasn'tgraceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamonqueen.
Even watching the bourbonflow.
Ha!
That devil in abottle.
It whispers candylies.
A liquid Trojanhorse.
A burning sweetsurprise.
Shot after shot wentdown.
Smooth as a velvetglove.
You lost all track of reason and lost all track oflove.
Orsobriety.
The silence of theforest.
Shattered by thesound.
Of all that cinnamonwhiskey.
Fighting the wrong wayround.
Oh,
but3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then amoan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plasticthrone.
And I was your humble servant in the palemoonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all mymight.
It wasn't wine androses.
It wasn'tgraceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamonqueen.
Even watching the bourbonflow.
Now some guys get asiren.
A goddess on apedestal.
Mine was kneelingover.
Looking ratherdreadful.
But as I held your forehead andwhispered,
"It's allright."
My love was shining clearer than the stars on that coldnight.
It's not the perfectmoments.
It's the ones we survive that prove you're still the only one who makes me feelalive.
Ohyeah,
3:00
AM came calling with a crash and then amoan.
You woke me from my slumber clutching the plasticthrone.
And I was your humble servant in the palemoonlight.
Holding back your lovely head with all mymight.
It wasn't wine androses.
It wasn'tgraceful,
no.
But you're my cinnamonqueen.
Even watching the bourbonflow.
Yeah.
My cinnamonqueen.
A crown of messyhair.
Worship in the trashcan.
But I'll always be rightthere.