Coffee's cold on thecounter.
Fifty sets of boots by thedoor.
The TV'sloud,
cam and stuff being scattered like a technicolorstorm.
I'm just trying to find mykeys.
You're in the center of thebreeze,
handling it all with suchease.
And I'm just caught here in theview.
Watching all the things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane.
A whispering word that stops therain.
It's an instinct I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
Right.
A nose bleed and a suddencry,
you're there before the tear candry.
A quietword,
a healingkiss,
there's no problem you can'tdismiss.
You're ajudge,
anurse,
astoryteller.
A fortress in asoft,
warmpillow.
You see the world right through their eyes without a hint ofcompromise.
And I'm just caught here in theview.
Watching all the things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane.
A whispering word that stops therain.
It's an instinct I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
Oh,
right.
I try my best to play mypart,
but you're therhythm,
you're theheart.
You don't just build ahouse,
you build ahome.
You plant the seeds and watch them grow with a patience I will neverknow.
Oh.
You're the calmest place I've everknown.
And I'm just caught here in theview.
Watching all the things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane.
A whispering word that stops therain.
It's an instinct I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
The way youmother.
It's a quietstrength.
I'm just watchingyou.
Making everythingright.
My amazingwife.
My amazingmother.