Coffee's cold on thecounter.
Fifty sets of boots by thedoor.
The TV'sloud,
cam- and stuff being scattered like a technicolorstorm.
I'm just trying to find mykeys.
You're in the center of thebreeze,
handling it all with such anease.
And I'm just caught here in theview,
watching all things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane,
the whispered word that stops therain.
It's aninstant,
I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
Ah.
A nose bleed and a suddencry,
you're there before the tear candry.
A quietword,
a healingkiss,
there's no problem you can'tdismiss.
You're ajudge,
anurse,
astoryteller.
A fortress in a soft warmpillow.
You see the world right through theireyes,
without a hint ofcompromise.
And I'm just caught here in theview,
watching all the things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane,
the whispered word that stops therain.
It's aninstinct,
I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
.
I try mybest,
I play mypart,
but you're therhythm,
you're theheart.
You don't just build ahouse,
you build ahome.
You plant the seeds and watch themgrow,
with a patience I will neverknow.
Ooh.
You're the calmest place I've everknown.
And I'm just caught here in theview,
watching all the things youdo.
You're the calm inside thehurricane,
the whispered word that stops therain.
It's aninstinct,
I can'tunderstand,
how you heal the world just with yourhand.
It's a quietstrength,
a guidinglight.
Oh,
the way youmother,
making everythingright.
The way youmother.
It's a quietstrength.
I'm just watchingyou.
Making everythingright.
My amazingwife,
my amazingmother.