Another Tuesdaymorning,
same oldroutine.
The vanitymirror,
a shallowscene.
They're tradin'secrets,
whispers in thehall.
Did you see what she waswearin'?
It's justawful,
y'all.
Pink manicures and little whitelies,
they spend their whole damn paycheck on what moneybuys.
Little bows and kittenheels,
scared to break asweat.
Oh,
they call itlivin',
but they haven't learned to liveyet.
'Cause real women driveJeeps,
baby,
rooftopdown,
tearin' up the blacktop all over thistown.
Got the sun in ourfaces,
dust in ourhair.
Don't need a paved road 'cause we don't reallycare.
Spinnin' the tires on a path of ourown,
got the radioblastin',
drivin' hard to thebone.
Yeah,
real women driveJeeps,
can you hear thatsound?
The only gossip we're spreadin' is the bass that shakes theground.
They're filterin' pictures till their skin ispristine.
Afraid of asmudge,
afraid of what's real andmean.
Obsessed with the weight on that digitalscale,
their biggest problem is a brokenfingernail.
They spend all their hours just tryna fit themold,
another copy of a story that's alreadytold.
Hidin' from theweather,
shieldin' theircomplexion,
just a fragile little doll cravin' cheapaffection.
'Cause real women driveJeeps,
baby,
rooftopdown,
tearin' up the blacktop all over thistown.
Got the sun in ourfaces,
dust in ourhair.
Don't need a paved road 'cause we don't reallycare.
Spinnin' the tires on a path of ourown,
got the radioblastin',
drivin' hard to thebone.
Yeah,
real women driveJeeps,
can you hear thatsound?
The only gossip we're spreadin' is the bass that shakes theground.
Real women driveJeeps.
Rooftopdown.