Yeah.
Sun'shigh,
waterclear.
Reflections on theglass.
I'm chillin' on the shore lettin' summer dayspass.
Then the sceneshifts,
the vibe lifts as you come intoview.
A vision on thewater,
everything brandnew.
This ain't no mud boatridin',
no four-wheel drivesound.
Just a simple board beneath you glidin' without asound.
But there's grace in yourmotion,
the way you ride thebreeze.
Got me pausin' myworld,
sinkin' to myknees.
Paved roadsdisappear,
street lights out ofsight.
Just the shimmer of the lake bathed in goldenlight.
I've seen the glitz andglamour,
heard the big citybeat.
But the silent elegance youhold,
man,
it just can't bebeat.
Oh,
the red paddle queen settin' fire to thetide.
That scarlet wave of hair where the sunlight loves tohide.
You glide where the currentsflow,
you're on a liquidstream.
With everystroke,
everymove,
you can't bebeat.
On the board in thebreeze,
you're the only sight Ineed.
The red paddlequeen,
a natural beautyindeed.
From a distance I could tell you're a man of yourspace.
Got that countryfocus,
that clear look on yourface.
Then you turn toward the banks and your smile hits the air like an instant dose ofsunshine,
showin' you don't care about thegossip,
thenoise,
the usualdistractions.
You're plugged into themoment,
pure physics andreactions.
I admire thebalance,
thecontrol,
the silentpower.
Like you're walkin' on the surface in your own specifichour.
The paved roadsdisappear,
the street lights out ofsight.
Just the shimmer of the lake bathed in goldenlight.
I've seen the glitz andglamour,
heard the big citybeat.
But the silent elegance youhold,
man,
it just can't bebeat.
Oh,
the red paddle queen settin' fire to thetide.
That scarlet wave of hair where the sunlight loves tohide.
You glide where the currentsflow,
you're on a liquidstream.
With everystroke,
everymove,
you can't bebeat.
On the board in thebreeze,
you're the only sight Ineed.
The red paddlequeen,
a natural beautyindeed.
Oh.
Oh,
yeah.
Oh.
Yeah,
the perfect hue on a canvas ofblue.
You make the simple act look like somethin' brandnew.
It's more than just apaddle,
more than just aride.
It's the confidence you carry with nothin' left tohide.
Gotta watch that hair flip one moretime,
nolie.
Oh,
the red paddle queen settin' fire to thetide.
That scarlet wave of hair where the sunlight loves tohide.
You glide where the currentsflow,
you're on a liquidstream.
With everystroke,
everymove,
you can't bebeat.
On the board in thebreeze,
you're the only sight Ineed.
The red paddlequeen,
a natural beautyindeed.
Oh.
Red paddlequeen.
Yeah,
that's thewave.
AMr.
Unjust Wantproject.
Country trapflow.
Smooth on thewater.