Hallelujah,
I'm gonna bealright.
The bossman'syelling,
my desk's amess.
Deadlinescircling,
Iconfess.
The coffee'scold,
my patiencethin.
This nine to five feels like asin.
But then I seeher,
that red headedlight.
Her smile burns through my darkestnight.
OhHallelujah,
I'm gonna bealright.
Two boysscreaming,
the house iswild.
Spilledmilk,
rivers and tantrumtrials.
I'm just oneman,
I feel sosmall.
How do I answer their everycall?
But then I seeher,
that red headedlight.
Her smile burns through my darkestnight.
OhHallelujah,
I'm gonna bealright.
Breath isshort,
my chest istight.
The walls areclosing,
I lose thefight.
The world spinsfast,
I'm on myknees.
I cry forhelp,
Lord,
hear meplease.
But then I seeher,
that red headedlight.
Her smile burns through my darkestnight.
OhHallelujah,
I'm gonna bealright.