♪ Mm mm mm mm ♪ The boss man'syellin'.
My desk's amess.
Deadlinescirclin'.
Iconfess.
The coffee'scold.
My patiencethin.
This nine to five feels like asin.
But then I seeher.
That red headedlight.
Her smile burns through my darkestnight.
Oh oh oh ohhallelujah.
I'm gonna be allright.
Oohhallelujah.
Two boysscreamin'.
The house iswild.
Spilledmilk,
rivers and tantrumtrials.
I'm just oneman.
I feel sosmall.
How do I answer their everycall?
But then I seeher.
That red headedlight.
Her smile burns through my darkestnight.
Oh oh oh ohhallelujah.
I'm gonna be allright.
Woo!
Hallelujah.
I'm gonna be allright.
Breath isshort.
My chest istight.
The walls areclosin'.
I lose thefight.
The world spinsfast.
I'm on myknees.
I cry forhelp.
Lord,
hearme,
please.
But then I seeher.
That red headedlight.
Ohoh,
her smile burns through my darkestnight.
Oh oh oh ohhallelujah.
I'm gonna be allright.
Ohhallelujah.