No.
Wait.
Thewaves,
theyroared,
the night wasblack,
a lantern swung on the captain'srack.
But there she swam with hair of flame and called me out by my ownname.
Oh,
the crimsontide,
it pulled menear.
Her voice likegold,
her smile soclear.
A red-haired mermaid stole my heart and dragged me down to where dreamsstart.
Hey.
Her eyes were green like kelp atdawn,
her laughter rang like a siren'ssong.
I reached myhand,
she held it tight and pulled me deep into thenight.
What's a man to do at sea when a mermaid sets his spiritfree?
Oh,
the crimsontide,
it pulled menear.
Her voice likegold,
her smile soclear.
A red-haired mermaid stole my heart and dragged me down to where dreamsstart.
Hey.
Oh.
The ocean'sdepths,
they hold nofear,
not when her whispers fill myear.
No compassnow,
nostars,
nomap,
just her soft kiss and the waves thatclap.
Oh,
the crimsontide,
it pulled menear.
Her voice likegold,
her smile soclear.
A red-haired mermaid stole my heart and dragged me down to where dreamsstart.
Hey.
Oh.