My best friend had an artclass,
I think it was101.
They talked aboutPicasso,
and what to do forfun.
He sat beside a girl heknew,
they chatted 'bout theweek.
And somehow they got on the topic of a bit ofmystique.
She said she'd always wondered but never took thechance.
My buddysaid,
"I know aguy,
let'scircumstance."
He calls me up on my flipphone,
says,
"Man,
I need afavor.
My friend wants theexperience,
can you supply theflavor?"
Hesaid,
"You know the goodstuff,
you got the masterplan."
Isaid,
"Yeah,
I'm yourguy.
I'll do what Ican."
Just anotherTuesday,
a simple youthfulquest.
I had no idea it was a cosmictest.
We met up on aSaturday,
as I rememberwell.
And that's the day I saw your face and stumbled where Ifell.
You had that long redhair,
and freckles and a choker on yourneck.
My brain just wentoffline,
I was a totalwreck.
The mission was afailure,
a total epicbust.
But I didn't evennotice,
I found my sacredtrust.
Who needs the good stuff when I'm looking atyou?
My whole world changed thatafternoon.
We stood there kindaawkward,
kicking gravel with ourshoes.
I was trying to becharming,
probably breaking all therules.
You talked about your paintings and the bands you loved themost.
I just kept onnodding,
acting like your humblehost.
My contact wasn'tanswering,
my other guy wasdry.
Our little rebel outing was a kissgoodbye.
My friend was soembarrassed,
said,
"Sorry,
this islame."
I just stood theresmiling,
trying to remember my ownname.
Hesaid,
"Man,
this is adisaster,"
as he hung up thephone.
Isaid,
"I don't knowman,
I'm feeling kinda blownaway."
We met up on aSaturday,
as I rememberwell.
And that's the day I saw your face and stumbled where Ifell.
You had that long redhair,
and freckles and a choker on yourneck.
My brain just wentoffline,
I was a totalwreck.
The mission was afailure,
a total epicbust.
But I didn't evennotice,
I found my sacredtrust.
Who needs the good stuff when I'm looking atyou?
My whole world changed thatafternoon.
It's funny how a stupidplan,
a half-baked high school plot could be the single greatest stroke of luck I evergot.
We were just kids trying to find a littlebuzz,
but I found my forever rightthere.
Just because I saw thefuture,
I saw the white hairs and the wrinkledhands.
I saw the family we would build on these suburbanlands.
We met up on aSaturday,
as I rememberwell.
And that's the day I saw your face and stumbled where Ifell.
You had that long redhair,
and freckles and a choker on yourneck.
My brain just wentoffline,
I was a totalwreck.
The mission was afailure,
a total epicbust.
But I didn't evennotice,
I found my sacredtrust.
Who needs the good stuff when I'm looking atyou?
My whole world changed thatafternoon.
Yeah,
we never gothigh,
not in the way wemeant.
But you're the best thing that was everheaven-sent.
The plan went up in smoke before it evenlit.
But finding you was the ultimatehit.
Yeah,
you're the goodstuff.
You alwayswere.