I check thethermostat,
read the outsideair.
It says don't go out there without a properpair.
I'm zipping up myjacket,
putting gloves on myhand.
Preparing for the freeze that grips this northernland.
But I hear the click-clack coming down thehall.
Like she's stepping off the sand right past the gardenwall.
Ooh.
I don't even askher,
I alreadyknow.
She's got a secret summer in the middle of thesnow.
Shesays,
"I need myfreedom,
need to feel thefloor."
Then she grabs her heavy coat and heads right for thedoor.
She's walking on the zero-degreebeach.
The comfort of thatplastic,
nothing else canreach.
She's walking on the zero-degreebeach.
A beautiful stubborn habit that the cold can'tteach.
No matter if it's autumn or a Januarysleet.
She's got the only summer that exists beneath herfeet.
My quirky queen in her flip-flops all yearlong.
We went to awedding,
the venue was sogrand.
White gloves and polished shoes across the marbleland.
She looked like a millionbucks,
every hair was inplace.
Except for that telltale sign of her personalspace.
When she kicked off her heels just an hour after thedance.
And swapped in the cheap sandals with an affectionateglance.
Said,
"These are the trueme,
this is how Ithrive.
The only person keeping Californiaalive."
Other peoplestare,
they give a littlelook.
But they don't know the comfort that she's found inside thathook.
They don't know thestory,
thededication,
thepieces.
Got her priorities and they're never gonnasee.
She's walking on the zero-degreebeach.
The comfort of thatplastic,
nothing else canreach.
She's walking on the zero-degreebeach.
A beautiful stubborn habit that the cold can'tteach.
No matter if it's autumn or a Januarysleet.
She's got the only summer that exists beneath herfeet.
My quirky queen in her flip-flops all yearlong.
It's just a little thing Iknow,
an insignificanttrait.
But it's one of those small wonders that Icelebrate.
You found the perfect lifehack,
the ultimaterelease.
You choose your ownweather,
you choose your ownpeace.
All yearlong.
Ooh.
A zero-degreebeach.
Yeah,
all yearlong.
Ooh.